# ANA M GONZALEZ

- ana.m.gonzalez0496@gmail.co
- h (954) 805-6743
- a Miami, FL 33147

anamariagonzalez.info

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Determined Full Stack Web Developer offering expertise in fast-paced departments. Bilingual and well-spoken with ability to work closely with people of all different backgrounds and personalities. Driven to continuously grow expertise in website development, programming and code testing. Desiring a challenging and growth-oriented position.

## **SKILLS**

- React js, Gatsby
- · Ruby on Rails
- JavaScript, HTML, CSS(Sass)
- J-Query
- Adobe Creative Cloud, Sketch
- · Netlify, Firebase
- API intergrations
- · Testing and results analysis

### **EDUCATION**

Wyncode Academy
Miami, FL • 02/2019

#### Full Stack Web Development

· Received Spirit of Wyncode Award

University of Miami Miami, FL • 05/2018

**Bachelor of Arts:** Painting/Graphic Design

New World School of The Arts Miami, FL • 05/2014

#### High School Diploma

- · Magna cum laude graduate
- Ranked in Top 5% of class

#### **WORK HISTORY**

ReachLink - Junior Web Developer Boca Raton, FL • 03/2019 - 08/2019

- Collaborated with other developers to build a mobile-first HTML, CSS, JavaScript and j-Query responsive site
- · Managed Software API integrations
- Built and managed Twilio Web APIs for seamless programs for phone, text, and other communication functions
- Applied knowledge of JavaScript and Object-Oriented Programming to create successful designs

## International Association of Curators of Contemporary Art - Technical Project Manager

Miami Beach, FL • 03/2017 - 02/2019

- Collaborated with business users, technical teams, database administrators and testing teams, to analyze, gather, and validate requirements such as kickoff meetings, joint application designing and planning sessions
- · Social Media manager and volunteer hiring coordinator

#### ArtSail - Website Developer

Miami Beach, FL • 01/2018 - 12/2018

- Designed the ArtSail website in collaboration with the Frost Museum of Science
- Kept abreast of emerging technologies, software and trends and applied them to projects
- Oversaw troubleshooting of technical issues to solve problems within reasonable timeframe